Hello hello everyone welcome to
Stock Market Tak channel so friends in
this experiment we are going to talk about the day one subscription status of
Star Health Insurance IPO after the end of the first day, the
IPO was not completed on the first day,
despite this how many of you people have been
seen subscribing and
which names did you see in the anchor investor list,
apart from this how much has been seen being disclosed according to the
latest update in the grey market of three more IPOs
and
you can take a decision here related to whether to apply or avoid it and from this point of
view you
can apply in this IPO, Govinda was going to talk about all these points
one by one in this video,
watch its blaster so that you do not get any important
information, before this
two more important videos have been uploaded on this channel for all of you friends,
first one is
Colors and Sakant here and this is how you can get complete details of
Anand Rathi IPO which is going to open on 9th December
Both of these have been reviewed, whatever you do is given
in the description box of this video below and on this skin
you
can pause both these videos from there for study,
typing on this and stock market sir,
for latest updates subscribe to the channel and also
select the bell icon for all so that whenever we
upload such informative videos
you will get notifications mission tips, it is good that to
increase your slots, you
could have increased your profit by applying which 19, you can take advantage of meeting end, so till now
your family has
not opened his demat account, then just
adopt four things, PAN card, Aadhar
card and cancelled cheque and signature and
you people keep all these things, so
unfortunately I have
written the method in the description box of the video, from there you can increase your profit by
closing your pimples change free mode and
applying in the coming good village,
if you do Star Health
Insurance APO here, today is the
date to apply,
today here is the first here  So first we will
see how many subscribers have been subscribed.
Also, in the IPO, you have to wait for tomorrow's date.
Here, friends, in what way can
you see the subscription status tomorrow?
Whether some positive momentum is seen in the grey market place
or not, then only you
can consider applying here for listing and for interview Saturday.
By the way, what will be my final decision, you have to wait for
applying in this video.
Tomorrow 526, we will get a clear update related to it in the
video that will come in this manner.
Whatever will be there, you can do it there so that
you people get the update. The
last date to apply is going to be in the
beginning of December and while applying here,
you people have to apply at the cutter price here,
it is not soft, so if
you apply at the cutter price only, then you will
get allotment. Chances and
possibility of buying weapons here, so here the number
of people has
increased a lot, due to this, the share here
is worth Rs 249 crore.  Due to this reason, you people did
not get to see the entire overall subscription here on the first day. The
total over subscription is not seen happening in any way for BJP.
Qualified Institutional Investors are not like that
and neither are retailers. If we
talk about it after the end of the day, then here
0.00 times subscriptions were seen by Qualified Institutional Investors here
but on the
first day of Urmila, you did
not get to see any response from them. Also,
talking about the channel category, Network,
Individual, Inverter, Everyone, Institutional
Investor, they also have 0.01 time
schedule subscription by both of them. Generally,
you people see that whatever you get to see here,
you people will see
positive and negative response from them after 12:00 on the third day, on that,
later point is
seen for the entire picture. So, it is a
matter to be seen
tomorrow, in what way you  The updates that come from people are
also going to be very important.
Also, if we talk from the retailers' portion,
here through retail individual injection,
you people have subscribed 0.64 time schedule, that is, as of
yesterday,
in this position, you will
see the plots subscribed in this category. Also, if we talk about the apply category, then
0.03 time schedules were seen being
subscribed.
If we talk about the option, after the end of the first day,
you will see
0.22186 interested or not. Approximately
12% of the total time schedules were seen being subscribed on the first day,
which means that
it did not get a good response. You can
talk about
how many shares have been referred to you for qualified institutional investors. So, to
apply here, two crore and 38 lakh 30
thousand 602 equity shares will be offered and if we
talk about this according to the value, then  If we
talk about Heroin Kolkata Admit of Rs 2640 crore, then the amount
offered for them here was Rs 1 crore
19 lakh 15,300 and if we talk here as per the value,
that is Rs 1 thousand for 14 years, it is
better for you people to
reach here and if we
talk about retail investor creativity, then 79 lakh 43
thousand 535 equity shares were offered and
7000 sorry here seven thousand sorry here
714 crore that here you people can
apply here on the valuation, that is, death
sentence has been kept reserved for retailers in this IPO,
talk about coming here and
listening bag here, companies Star
Health Insurance here, which are anchor
investors as anchor investors,
how much did they invest here and on the first day itself, the
date of opening of your office
number is 3217 crore, people have been seen
subscribing here
as anchor investors, on the
29th of number here, how many anchor
investors  If you see them participating, then the
last 2 anchor investors have
participated here. This IPO is
used by you people, it is
opened for investors, you have been
subscribed here and the anchor investor has been told that there is
gas refilling here, you
people have been told that they have invested Rs. 3
crore 57 lakh 45 thousand 921 share knowledge
and its cutter price, you can see subscribing to it here,
here as anchor investors, you can see the foreign
institutional investors investing here, here
you
people have got the comment of Singapore New Economic
Fund by the Singapore Government and here if you people have become W Fashion
Smaller Rupee Company point and
talk here Abu Dhabi Investment
Authority, here all these matters are infamous
here, you have seen people
investing in this company as anchor investors, if we
talk about how to automate inverters then it is
Asian Life Insurance.
HDFC Life Insurance Max Life
Insurance Let's first look at the Special Economic Zone for Unity Fund, which has
become the Indian Ashram Life Insurance Fund
offer. All these investors have been seen
investing here as dominated anchor investors. If we
talk about the anchor investor list, then a good
anchor investor list has been seen
here. Now, if
you want to supply the listing end
quantum, then you can apply for this IPO by paying the
subscription status and market premium on yesterday's date.
Here, the latest
grey market yield of Adani Wilmar IPO can be seen here.
Here,
Ranipur Marathis was seen trading at 125 in the grey market.
There, by clicking the
next tab, if we talk about the latest, then
Tega Industries IPO, the
opening date of this IPO is going to be from tomorrow. How many of you are going to
apply in this IPO and
how many are applying for loans, you
can take it in the comments. Morning
Mrs. Bramble - was trading at 370
but the latest one was at 1 pm.  According to the updated grey market
premium, it has been
seen trading at four to five, that is, if we
talk about cut blouse, then it is 453, in that
₹4000, you people add here,
here you people used to see the listing price at 858, we have
talked about it in detail, then it is seen
trading at a premium of 90%, that is, those who will get
allotment of money in IPO, they get to see their money doubling
because here the
suicide is less, so you people can increase the allotment by
comparing and liking in every house here, if we
talk about the next video, then Anand Rathi Wealth is yours, by doing this,
here it is that you
people have approved the complete
details review video related to it on 9th December 09, you
people should
get the link of it in the description box that
you people were
debiting the ATM of Mrs. Bramble on Invest In in the morning and
here the latest grey market which was presented at 1 pm was
seen trading at 40
That is, if we talk about the cut-off price, then if we
add 140 to 550, then the
price has to be kept more than 60 and if we
talk according to this, then it has been seen trading at a premium of 34 percent,
according to the head of Tak Rahman, but the
bill for applying point Aamir is thankfully, sub-
station status poetry, well,
you can apply this creative from 0.2,
next here the planet of Star Health Insurance
IPO was setting sixteen in the marketing morning
and is, but the
latest update was seen adding on Prem Office stage, that is,
you will see 90128 on 68th, then 09:16 PM East
Paraguay and according to this, it will be
seen trading at a premium of only 2% here,
in the coming time, if there is a
good subscription response in yesterday's date, then only you will get to
see a good song, if it is
good in the grey market then only you
people can go and apply it, but quantum, so I
hope you people can like and comment on all this information.
By the way, you people used to get updates about buying Delhi's grey
market mixture,
which will continue so that you get updates
because Singh Ibrahim thanks for
watching this video, so that new
information should be taken till then.